

ABOUT ME

Front-End Developer with 5 year of experience. Can create high-quality solutions using key skills: HTML/CSS, Javascript, JQuery, React, Magento 2, Shopify, Shopware 6, PrestaShop, WordPress. A high level of communication helps me solve problems that may arise in the project.

SKILLS



LINKS

Telegram: @kate_koval95

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ekat erina-kovaliova-9694a1170/

Portfolio:

https://kovaliova.github.io/Portfolion React/

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

BEI ORUSSIAN

KATE KOVALIOVA FRONT END DEVELOPER

Warsaw, Poland

572 180 396

🔀 kate1996970@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

BELVG

Minsk Sep 2020 - Present

Front End Developer

- · Work with various commercial projects.
- · Communication with customers (correspondence, calls).
- · Daily calls with the team.
- Working with CMS Shopify, Shopware 6, Magento 2, PrestaShop, WordPress.

AURIUS STUDIO

Minsk Jul 2019 - Aug 2020

Front End Developer

- Website layout for a unique design, pulling on its own CMS.
- · Work on commercial projects.

7TOP.BY

Minsk Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

Web Programmer

- · Development of websites with unique design.
- Website development using CMS (Wordpress, ModX, Opencart).
- · Work on commercial projects.

UPWORK

Poland Feb 2024 - Present

Frelancer

Development of online stores, refinement of existing stores in the commercial sector.

Working with CMS Shopify, Shopware 6, Magento 2, PrestaShop, WordPress.

EDUCATION

BSUIR-MINSK

Minsk 2017

COURSES

- Adobe Certified Professional Adobe Commerce Front-End
 Developer
- Web application development with Javascript
- Web development using React & Angular